The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Father...
Noooo !!!
It's time for dinner.
Hurry, let's eat.
Father,
Mother,
I miss you so much...
so much...
I didn't expect
that I would be able
to condense my killing intent even further.
My state of heart wasn't right before.
Ceng Da Niu
Woaaa !
Did Uncle make this ?
So cool.
What's the matter ?
Oh, right.
I came to give you this.
Now when a guest comes in,
you will know.
This is for you.
Thank you Uncle !
Uncle,
my name is Da Niu.
I'm from the blacksmith across the street.
Remember to come and play with me.
Ceng Niu
Ceng Da Niu's father
Dad, Mom !
Look at this !
The uncle across the street gave it to me.
Ceng Si
Ceng Da Niu's mother
Here, let me see.
Such an exquisite wood carving !
You little ignorant rascal !
Ouch, it hurts.
Brother,
excuse him.
The kid doesn't understand.
How much does it cost ?
I gifted it to him,
it's just a piece of wood after all.
You just arrived, right ?
The shop across the street has been empty for years.
Brother,
if you don't mind,
come over for a meal.
I have homemade wine.
It's much better than the wine in restaurants !
Okay.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
We'll be neighbors from now on.
Let's go !
I'll show you around.
How long has it been since I last ate ?
I stopped eating at Foundation Establishment.
Does it not suit your taste ?
Brother,
We only have this simple food.
I'm sorry.
I like it.
Come on, eat this.
Since you just arrived here,
you aren't familiar with this place.
If you need anything,
let us know.
As neighbours, we should help each other.
If you need groceries,
go to the Li Family's shop,
it's good and affordable.
The Xu Family's shop is expensive
but the people are kind.
I heard that their young master is very successful.
He's following the Crown Prince.
The craft of brewing wine is passed down in our family.
Try it.
It's a good wine !
Come on, one more.
Come on, eat more. Cheers.
1 year later
Uncle Wang,
what kind of animal is this ?
It looks like a turtle
but its head is weird.
It's a kind of ancient creature.
Although it looks like this,
in reality it's fierce
and powerful.
It sounds so cool !
10 days later
Uncle Wang,
I'm here to deliver the wine.
This is a fire spider.
It has a violent temperament
and its 8 legs are very sharp.
Don't get hurt by one.
This is so interesting !
Dad !
I don't want to be a blacksmith.
I want to learn wood carving !
What the hell are you talking about ?
You cannot even hold a forge hammer properly,
yet you want to do fine work like Uncle Wang ?
You little rascal !
Ouch !
Like a breeze,
4 seasons have already gone by.
Because my cultivation is limited,
I cannot carve Soul Formation cultivators.
But it doesn't matter,
the journey is long.
I carved my memories,
the villagers of the Wang Family,
Spirit Beasts I have faced.
They seem to have been reborn
when I carve them this way.
When I condense a fourth bead,
the killing intent will disappear.
Look at this !
It's a great wood carving.
Indeed !
It's really good.
Not bad...
It's like a real one.
Look at this one !
Let's look at this one.
Everyone praises how good they are,
but no one buys them.
Master Xu is coming back.
Master Xu follows the Crown Prince
he's a great man now !
Come, have a look !
Da Niu,
let go of me, okay ?
Master Xu,
look at these wood carvings.
They are better than those of the Zhou Family.
So... Will you buy one ?
Xu Tao
Don't sell it too expensive.
When you touch these wood carvings,
it feels strange right ?
I usually just look at them.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Sir, what kind of animal is it ?
Why does it look like a snake to me ?
This is a Flood Dragon !
It's an immortal creature !
A Flood Dragon ?
How much does this carving cost ?
10 taels of gold.
No...
it's so over...
Thank you, sir.
I want this wood carving.
Goodbye.
10 taels of gold ?
His Highness loves beautiful carvings.
The Crown Prince is principled,
if I give him this carving
he will praise me for sure.
Your Highness,
Xu Tao wants to see you.
Thank you, your Highness.
What's going on ?
We can talk tomorrow.
Your Highness,
I found a wood carving I think you will like.
If his Highness sees it,
he will understand.
Crown Prince
8th layer of Qi Condensation
Your Highness, don't touch it !
This is a treasure.
You have done a great service !
Let's go.
Come with me to see my father.
Mortal King
Zhou Qiao
White Could Sect disciple
Late stage Foundation Establishment
Weng Qi
White Cloud Sect disciple
Early stage Core Formation
Why did you come to see me ?
Weren't you having fun ?
Father, look.
This is...
This is a wood carving.
Senior Brother, of course I know this is a wood carving !
I mean, what is this a carving of ?
I haven't seen it before.
Immortal Elders,
is there anything special about this carving ?
This wood carving...
the higher your cultivation
the more you are affected by it.
But for mortals,
the effect is small.
This object
is not a normal carving.
The creature that is carved is almost the same
as the Flood Dragon in the ancient records of our sect.
But you said you had not seen it before...
It doesn't mean
that I didn't recognize it.
This means...
this object is a real treasure !
Guards,
Reward the Crown Prince with gold, silver and jade.
Your Highness,
where did you
find this wood carving ?
This...
So many treasures...
We're rich !
Junior Brother,
we're rich !
What ?!
Senior Brother,
this place is terrifying.
The greater the risk,
the greater the gains.
Come on.
Teleportation !?
This...
Why is a Nascent Soul cultivator here !?
You dared provoke the fiend,
you're doomed !
And I am the one who will devour your souls !
Dead...
We're so dead...
That will be a total of 4500 taels of gold.
Pay up.
Paying respects to Senior,
Juniors are disciples of the White Cloud Sect.
We didn't know these carvings were Senior's.
We are sorry for what we did,
please forgive us.
4500 taels of gold...
Do you have enough ?
Senior,
I have some spirit stones.
I don't have the gold mortals use.
He won't kill them ?
How unfortunate...
Get out.
Next time,
bring enough money.
Wait for me !
The killing intent is gone.
The Spring Festival is coming.
This is a token of goodwill from the Crown Prince.
His Highness said,
that if Master Immortal needs help in the future,
he's more than willing to help you out.
Happy New Year !
Happy New Year Brother Liu !
It's New Year already !
Uncle Wang,
why have I never seen these carvings before ?
Are they new ?
They are the first I made,
these carvings...
are my family.
Uncle Wang,
my father told me
that shopkeeper Lu tried to marry his daughter to you.
Why did you refuse ?
I have secretly spied on her
and she is gorgeous !
Uncle has a wife.
Really ?
How come I have never seen her ?
She's waiting for me in a far away place.
One day,
I'll go back to her.
Wow !
She's so pretty.
I've had my share of wounds,
now I want to fight back.
Is my destiny a wall of restrictions
that's blocking all my hopes
for life ?
My flesh and blood witnessed the past,
my adversity pushed me to brave the waves.
How do you navigate through the years passing by ?
Nirvana and rebirth are no longer
out of reach.
Immortals
are obsessed with delusions of grandeur.
Renegades
seek to crush the impermanence of the heavens.
Don't tell me that I overestimate myself
and that the path to revenge leads to hell
because I don't see the harm in that.
My new body opens its eyes
and awakens from its dream.
I have overcome many trials
to get this body back.
No matter how many endless dark nights go by,
I can still see.
By sticking to this thought, I will get it done
by my own hands.
Returning to my body opened my eyes,
I need to continue my Immortal journey.
With a flick of a finger,
only my indomitable heart remains.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.
Even if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,
like the descent of a god.